>> Brian Holt: 因此，您实际上可以使整个研讨会完全脱机，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So you can actually do
this entire workshop totally offline,
这对你也很有用
which is useful to you as well.
这是否有时我们的 IT 人员可能有问题
Whether that's maybe sometimes
our IT guy might have an issue or
你不在一个有互联网接入的地方
you're just not in a place
where have internet access.
在这种情况下，我们实际上已使 API 客户机工作 100% 脱机。
In that case, we've actually made it so
the API client works 100% offline.
所以我要向你们展示如何使这一工作更快地完成。
So I'm going to show you how to
make that work really quickly.
你想做的第一件事就是这里的命令
The first thing that you're gonna
wanna run is this command right here,
npm install-D 交叉 env。
npm install-D cross-env.
这是为了确保环境变量在 Linux中一致，
This is to make sure that environmental
variables were consistently across Linux,
还有麦克和窗户那就去吧
and Mac, and Window, so
go ahead and do that.
转至命令行。
Go to your command line.
去你的项目我们叫我们收养我
Go to your projects,
which we called ours adopt me,
并执行 npm install-D 交叉 env。
and do npm install-D cross-env.
> > Brian Holt: 好的，一旦您安装了该工具，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Okay,
once you have that tool installed,
那我要你把这个放进你的包里
then I want you to put this
inside of your package.json.
"dev:mock":cross -env PET_MOCK=模拟。
"dev:mock": cross-env PET_MOCK=mock.
这是用于 API 前进并使用模拟数据的信号。
This is the signal for
the API to go ahead and use the mock data.
然后执行 npm 运行 dev。
And then do npm run dev.
这只会执行同样的命令，但它会在不同的环境中运行。
And this will just do the same command but
it'll run it in a different environment.
这才是你要做的
And that's all that's going to do for you.
所以我要复制并粘贴这个 > > Brian Holt: Into my package.json。
So I'm just going to copy and paste this
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Into my package.json.
所以我已经在这里了但我要告诉你们这就是它所在的地方
So I actually have it already here but
I'll just show you this is where it is.
我把它放进去
And I'll just put that in there.
>> Brian Holt: 现在，如果我说 npm 运行 dev:mock，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Now,
if I say npm run dev:mock,
一切都一样
everything will work exactly the same.
>> Brian Holt: 除所有数据都将被嘲笑外，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Except all
the data will be mocked,
这意味着它永远不会点击 API。
which means it will never hit the API.
所以如果我要到这里来刷新页面
So if I go here to this,
refresh the page, and
你可以看到我的数据是非森森的对吧
there you can see I have nonsensical data,
right?
现在，这只是返回给您的随机数据。
Now, this is just returning
to you random data.
好消息是它是决定性的如果我去的话
The good news is that it is deterministic
in the sense that if I go to,
通知说这第二个叫 Jewelery
notice that this second one
here is called Jewelery.
如果我去 Cat ，它会给我一套不同的品种。
And if I go to Cat,
it will give me a different set of breeds.
但如果我回去做狗， >> Brian Holt:
But if I go back to dog,
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: It gives
我也有同样的数据，所以它可以可靠的和随机的东西一样。
me the same set of data as well, so it's
dependably the same list of random things.
所以如果你有我做的同样的问题那就是它不是在一个模拟的
So if you had the same problem that I did,
which is that it wasn't building in a mock
方式，只是除去，或者
mode, just do remove, or rather,
要执行的操作是您只想删除高速缓存和
what you want to do is you just
want to delete the cache and
dist 目录，因为有时解析处于陌生状态。
dist directories because sometimes
parse gets in a strange state.
所以如果你只强调这两者并说删除的话，
So if you just highlight those two and
say delete, and
然后重新运行 dev: 模拟，所有内容都应正确构建。
then rerun dev: mock,
everything should build correctly.